spaceotechnologies.com 2019-12-27

# Privacy Policy of Space-O Technologies

We, at Space-O Technologies, are committed to protecting the privacy of our visitors, for we do not spam, sell, rent, lease or give away the information to any third party/parties.

It is projected to describe how we use and process your personal information. Please ensure that by visiting and using spaceotechnologies.com, you are agreeing and accepting the policies that are described in this Privacy Policy.

This Privacy Policy also explains how we are going to use your personal information and what happens to any personal data that you provide to us. Moreover, we do update the policies of this page from time to time, so please keep reviewing the page on regular basis.

## 1\. Information We Collect

  * ## (i) Personal Information

The personal information that we may collect include name, contact information, IP addresses, product and service selections and other information, identifying you. We may also gather and collect personal information from you at different points, including but not limited to the following:

    * At the time of communicating with you as a customer or prospective customer;
    * When you prefer to visit our website or make use of the platform;
    * While registering you as an end-user of our products or services and one account is especially made for you;
    * When you fill our “Contact Us” form to get in touch with our experts;
  * ## (ii) Non-personal Data

We may also collect or gather non-personal data or information about users whenever they prefer to interact with our website. Non-personal data and information include the browser name that user access, the type of computer, technical information like operating system and Internet service providers and other similar information via Google Analytics.

## 2\. Cookies

Our website does not collect any information about users, except for the information contained in Cookies. Talking about cookies, they are small text files, which are mainly saved and retrieved information about your visit to our website. We use cookies to give personalized experienced on our website. Here, you can find how we use cookies:

  * **Session cookies:** generally, session cookies are cached mainly for the duration of your use of our website;
  * **Permanent cookies:** permanent cookies are stored in your terminal device for the time specified in the Cookie files parameters or until you delete.

You can adjust the settings on your computer in order to decline any cookies if you wish to.

## 3\. Disclosing Your Information

We assure you that we will not disclose your gathered personal information to any other party than in agreement with this Privacy Policy. Some of the circumstances given below when we may need to share your share:

  * In any situation, when we might have to sell any or all our business to the buyer.
  * We may disclose your personal information when it is legally required by the law.
  * To protect fraud and reduce the risk of fraud.

Space-O Technologies never sell, trade or rent users’ personal information to others. If required, we may share general demographic data and information that is not linked to any personal information regarding visitors with our trusted business partners, affiliates and advertisers for the purpose mentioned above.

## 4\. Security

Here, we make sure that your shared personal or non-personal information is safe and secure from any unauthorized access, use, loss or destruction. Personal or non-personal information that provided by you is stored on a safe and secured web server that is managed by Space-O Technologies. To protect from authorized access, we have used physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information.

## 5\. Third Party Links/Websites

Space-O Technologies may link to third-party websites and services when required; however, we are not responsible for privacy statements, practices or the contents of such third-party sites.

## 6\. Changes to Privacy Policy

Space-O Technologies reserves the right to change, edit or amend this Privacy Policy at any time without any prior notice. When we change, edit or remove any part from this privacy policy, we will mention the updated date at the bottom of this privacy policy page. We encourage our users to keep reviewing this page frequently in order to stay updated with the changes that we perform. The continuing use of our website means that you agree and accept those changes.

## 7\. Contact Us

In case, if you have any query or question regarding our Privacy Policy, you can get in touch with us at: <https://spaceotechnologies.com/contact-us/>

## Contact Address:

1005, 10th Floor, Abhishree Adroit, B/S Gwalia Sweet,  
Mansi Circle,  
Ahmedabad, Gujarat 380015  
Phone: +91 79 40084018  
Email: spaceo.inquiry@gmail.com
